<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<salon>
    <teamMember>
        <name>Rosemary Nguyen</name>
        <description>After getting her associates in cosmetics in the late 90s, she has worked in various salons before opening her first salon in Providence. She sold that business after 5 years to be with family for while before opening Perfect Nails with her husband closer to home. The community she built at her previous salon followed her to her new salon. To continue evolving her business, she begun to pursue another certification in 2012 for permanent makeup and eyelash extensions. Now offering a variety of services that people usually have to go to different locations for, Perfect Nails can become anyone's one stop salon.</description>
    </teamMember>

    <teamMember>
        <name>Andy Nguyen</name>
        <description>Andy has a gentle soul that comes across and makes many feel comfortable while being serviced by him. Having nearly as much experience as Rosemary, he helps keep the fort down and has become someone the team relies on.</description>
    </teamMember>

    <teamMember>
        <name>Tiffany Huynh</name>
        <description>As a mother, her caring yet bubbly energy is apparent. Having the most experience after Andy and Rosemary, she can skillfully do a manicure as if it was an art piece.</description>
    </teamMember>

    <teamMember>
        <name>Tina Huynh</name>
        <description>As the second youngest on the team, she is a great conversationalist and the biggest hype woman. She decorates her work station with cute knick knacks and is constantly making people laugh. Many have gone to her after a tiring day and left feeling like their problems desolved while getting their nails done.</description>
    </teamMember>

    <teamMember>
        <name>Lindsey Huynh</name>
        <description>The newest addition to Perfect Nails, she joined the team mid 2021. Lindsey helps to keep the atmosphere light while fine tuniing her skills everyday. She helps improve the salon by contributing a younger perspective and new ideas. Still developing her own unique art style, Lindsey can mimic and paint many finishing touch designs.</description>
    </teamMember>
    
    
</salon> 

 
            
        
 
           
 

